module three finding the right niche this is going to be helpful because the uh the more
specific that you know your audience right their problems what level they are in their problem
the more expertise it sounds like you have and you probably will it can be um here are some
examples right here and here's the exact equation who's your specific buyer it is not small
businesses it has to be more specific um in this example right just kind of pulled out of thin air
dental practices with two plus locations or um individuals in san francisco that are above this
income threshold be specific as possible and it'll help narrow down your audience what is the problem
is it painful and urgent that's going to be more likely for them to choose you today right if you
understand urgency if you understand um how exactly to beat out your competitors this is your call to
action this is your way to make them pay immediately context um this is this part right here
what else specifically about your audience is going to make them choose you you know more about linkedin
you know more about black friday because that's coming up you know about their specific platform
shopify whatever it is i help x solve y problem and then explain more about why you solve that specific
problem and then like i had mentioned be specific about your audience right that's just continuing on
here problem first validation signals um we don't have to go into too much detail here but this is just
going to help the sale the end part of your explanation here this is not necessarily going to be helpful
for your sales pitch is going to be helpful for getting them to click that stripe buy button
um swipe their credit card whatever it may be this is exactly what you need to understand in order to get
that final hurdle and then here is an example of the framework right you might have a niche that
isn't isn't too specific you're just as an example targeting any students someone that just a hobbyist
right someone who rides bikes occasionally and you offer the mountain biking service not exactly
perfect audience right you definitely want to narrow it down as perfectly i don't even want to say
perfectly narrow it down um as closely fit to your service as possible
and here's some more examples right there are tons of examples here so let's just quickly move on to
the next module here